Jonathan Chatfield

Gainesville, FL 32607 jonathan.chatfield@outlook.com +1 859 550 8835

I am an adaptable professional, who has been consistently called efficient and proactive by my coworkers and management. Over the course of my career, I have developed an ability to meet tight deadlines and I take constructive criticism well. I am a critical thinker that excels at problem solving. I possess excellent analytical skills and have been developing my Leadership Skills in every position I have held.

Work Experience

Data Analyst - Short Term Contract Grocery New Verticals Team

DoorDash

August 2022 to October 2022

Responsible for catalog for End User Grocery App and Catalog. Granular focus on purchasing trends and Dasher Errors to fine tune the Customer and Dasher experience. Worked to establish procedures in the department including SOP and Training Documentation.

Workforce Management Coordinator

Dynamic BDC

November 2019 to August 2022

Developed and maintained SOP Wiki using SharePoint for both Human Resources and Workforce Management Departments.

Responsible for scheduling, staffing projections and daily assignment for 300+ agents. Additionally responsible for daily, weekly, and monthly staffing and projections. Performed reporting specifically targeted on agent metrics. Excel and

PowerBI reporting and dashboarding. Handled hours and time reporting, including corrections. Compilation of CSAT Metrics and reporting, and additional Ad Hoc reporting as required.

Technical Support Supervisor

Kelly Services, Inc.

June 2017 to October 2019

Coaching and Development of Support Representatives. General Human Resources tasks

Supervisor/Coach

Sitel

January 2016 to May 2017

Responsible for a team of up to 30 customer service agents. Coaching and development in a Corporate Development plan. Participated in training for New

Hires as well as up training for tenured agents. Also responsible for most HR aspects for agents, including benefits requests, new hire paperwork completion, etc.

Content Writer / Editor

SharkBite Media

January 2016 to April 2017

Wrote list and subject content for multiple SEO campaigns. Developed topics and provided SEO optimized articles. Publishing and editing of other writer's work.

Assistant Call Center Manager

Teleperformance Advanced Services Division August 2010 to April 2016

Managed day to day operations of the account. Managed staffing levels, interface with client and led a team of supervisors to drive account performance.

• Quality Assurance Manager, HughesNet Account

Manage and Support Quality Analysts in monitoring and coaching of over 200 Technical Support Agents. Interface with Account Operations and Senior Management to deploy continual training and performance improvement, Daily Analysis and reporting of Customer Satisfaction trends and Quality Scores.

• Business Analyst, AT&T Account

Business analysis role. Advanced Excel Analytics and Data Trending. Creating reports for corporate management.

SQL Database Administrator/Network Administrator/Systems Administrator

Nova Southeastern University November 2005 to October 2007

Creation and Maintenance of Several SQL Server Databases, Data Analysis, and Reporting, Managed user group of approximately 200 Staff and Faculty through Active Directory, Exchange Server Maintenance and User Administration, provided Helpdesk support for all Students, Faculty and Staff.

Education

A.S. in Programming and Analysis

Santa Fe College

Present

Skills

- SOL
- System Administration
- · Microsoft SharePoint
- Network Administration
- LAN